<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://spring-bat.cloudvent.net//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://spring-bat.cloudvent.net//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-10-09T12:02:16+00:00</updated><id>https://spring-bat.cloudvent.net//feed.xml</id><title type="html">Treat Template</title><subtitle>Food blog template for Jekyll.</subtitle><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><entry><title type="html">8 Unfortunate People With The Same Names As Hated Celebrities Shared What It’s Like, And It’s Hilarious</title><link href="https://spring-bat.cloudvent.net//funny/2018/10/09/8-unfortunate-people-with-the-same-names-as-hated-celebrities-shared-what-its-like-and-its-hilarious/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="8 Unfortunate People With The Same Names As Hated Celebrities Shared What It’s Like, And It’s Hilarious" /><published>2018-10-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-10-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://spring-bat.cloudvent.net//funny/2018/10/09/8-unfortunate-people-with-the-same-names-as-hated-celebrities-shared-what-its-like-and-its-hilarious</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://spring-bat.cloudvent.net//funny/2018/10/09/8-unfortunate-people-with-the-same-names-as-hated-celebrities-shared-what-its-like-and-its-hilarious/">&lt;p&gt;Brett Kavanagh has never testified before a Senate committee and he’s never been accused of sexual assault, but he has had a very, very exhausting couple of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Donald Trump’s Supreme Court nominee, Brett Kavanaugh, dominated headlines, the 27-year-old clothing store supplier from Kentucky said he was mistaken for the politician on Twitter one too many times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I had a couple of beers and I was like ‘You know what, I’m just going to throw this out there,’” Kavanagh told the Louisville Courier Journal. “I thought to myself, ‘This is a terrible time to be named Brett Kavanagh.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So he tweeted this exact thought, and it went viral. “It was literally like a machine gun,” Kavanagh said. “It was like my phone caught a virus. It was constantly vibrating.” As of this article, over 1 million people have liked his tweet and more than 165K have retweeted it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even his boss was surprised by the whole ordeal. “I told him, ‘You’ve got to be kidding me.’” Goodson Clothing &amp;amp; Supply Co. owner, Landon Wade said. “It started with a joke here or there. But then it became crazy as the process went on.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the story of the Supreme Court nominee grew, so did the stress around Kavanagh’s work-life. Brett works in sales, and the first thing he leads a pitch with is his name. “The first thing I say is ‘My name is Brett Kavanagh,’” he said. “And literally the first reactions is ‘Wait, what did you just say.’ I have to stop and explain.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kavanagh said that going viral was something he has never anticipated. “I never use Twitter,” he added. “I had 127 followers. Now, I see that celebrities on Instagram are screenshotting it and my phone is just blowing up.” To his surprise, people who also share names with universally hated celebrities have been relating to him in the funniest ways. Susan Collins, Mike Pence, and many, many more have said that they know exactly how Kavanagh feels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recently, Donald Trump’s Supreme Court nominee, Brett Kavanaugh, has been dominating the headlines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html">Brett Kavanagh has never testified before a Senate committee and he’s never been accused of sexual assault, but he has had a very, very exhausting couple of weeks.</summary></entry></feed>